[
   {
    "option1": "He/It could gone.",
    "option2": "He/it can go.",
    "option3": "He/It could go.",
    "option4": "He/it can went.",
    "question": "সে/এ যেতে পারত",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Can he/it going ?",
    "option2": "Could he/it go ?",
    "option3": "Can he/it went ?",
    "option4": "Could he/it gone ?",
    "question": "সে/এ কি যেতে পারত ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "He/it can not be going.",
    "option2": "He/it can not went.",
    "option3": "He/it can not go.",
    "option4": "He/It could not go.",
    "question": "সে/এ যেতে পারল না",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "He/it will go.",
    "option2": "He/it should go.",
    "option3": "He/it perhaps went.",
    "option4": "Perhaps he/it will go.",
    "question": "সে/এ বোধহয় যাবে",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "He/it thought to go.",
    "option2": "He/it was think to going.",
    "option3": "He/It was thinking of going.",
    "option4": "He/it is thinking to go.",
    "question": "সে/এ যাবে ভাবছিল",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "He/It has to gone.",
    "option2": "He/It has to go.",
    "option3": "He/It is to go.",
    "option4": "He/It has gone.",
    "question": "তাকে/একে যেতে হবে",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Will he/it have to go ?",
    "option2": "Shall he/it has to go ?",
    "option3": "Will he/it have to gone ?",
    "option4": "Will he/it  to go ?",
    "question": "তাকে/একে কি যেতে হবে ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Will he/it not have to go ?",
    "option2": "Will he/it not has to go ?",
    "option3": "Was he/it not have to go ?",
    "option4": "Will he/it not have to gone ?",
    "question": "তাকে/একে কি যেতে হবে না ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "He/It need  going.",
    "option2": "He/It needs to go.",
    "option3": "He/It needs to going.",
    "option4": "He/It do needs to go.",
    "question": "তার/এর যাবার দরকার",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Why will he/it goes ?",
    "option2": "Why will he/it gone ?",
    "option3": "Why will he/it go ?",
    "option4": "Why will he/it going ?",
    "question": "সে/এ কেন যাবে ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Why will he/it not go ?",
    "option2": "Why shall he/it not go ?",
    "option3": "Why will he/it not gone ?",
    "option4": "Why will he/it do not go ?",
    "question": "কেন সে/এ যাবে না ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "When do he/it go ?",
    "option2": "When will he/it going ?",
    "option3": "When does he/it going ?",
    "option4": "When will he/it go ?",
    "question": "সে/এ কখন যাবে ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Where shall he/it go ?",
    "option2": "Where will he/it go ?",
    "option3": "Where will he/it goes ?",
    "option4": "Where will he/it going ?",
    "question": "সে/এ কোথায় যাবে ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "With whom will he/it go ?",
    "option2": "With whom was he/it go ?",
    "option3": "With who will he/it go ?",
    "option4": "With whom will he/it  be go ?",
    "question": "সে/এ কার সঙ্গে যাবে ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "He/It wants to going.",
    "option2": "He/It want to go.",
    "option3": "He/It wants to go.",
    "option4": "He/It wants to have go.",
    "question": "সে/এ যেতে চায়",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "He/It loves to go.",
    "option2": "He/It loves to gone.",
    "option3": "He/It love to go.",
    "option4": "He/It loves to going.",
    "question": "তার/এর যেতে ভালো লাগে",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "He/It wish to go.",
    "option2": "He/It wishes to go.",
    "option3": "He/It wished to go.",
    "option4": "He/It wishes to gone.",
    "question": "তার/এর যাবার ইচ্ছে আছে",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "If he/it could goes.",
    "option2": "If he/it can went.",
    "option3": "If he/it could go.",
    "option4": "If he/it can be going.",
    "question": "সে/এ যদি যেতে পারত",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]